|     |     |
| --- | --- |
|     | <br><br>UltraReach Internet Corporation Privacy Statement<br>=================================================<br><br>This document was last updated on October 2, 2021.<br><br>1. ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS<br>    <br>    UltraReach Internet Corporation is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the suite of tools we provide including Ultrasurf Windows Client, Ultrasurf Android VPN, Ultrasurf iOS VPN and Ultrasurf Chrome Extension. By using these tools, you acknowledge and fully understand freely consent to UltraReach Internet Corporation’s Privacy Statement.<br>    <br>2. PRIVACY STATEMENT<br>    <br>    To protect our users’ privacy and safety, UltraReach Internet Corporation does not require users to provide personal identifiable information to use our tools, users can download our tools and use them freely without disclosing their personal informaltion. Therefore, UltraReach Internet Corporation does not collect any personal identifiable information from its users.<br>    <br>    To protect our users’ privacy and safety, UltraReach Internet Corporation does not keep logs of users’ personal identifiable information, such as Internet Protocol Address (IP), web site visited, etc.<br>    <br>    Aggregate and/or De-identified Data<br>    <br>    In an ongoing effort to better understand our Website and users of the Website, we might analyze your information in aggregate and/or de-identified form to operate, maintain, manage, and improve the Website. This aggregate and/or de-identified information does not identify you personally. We may share this aggregate and/or de-identified data with our service providers, affiliates, agents, business partners and other third parties. We may also disclose aggregated and/or de-identified user statistics to current and prospective business partners and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.<br>    <br>3. CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT<br>    <br>    UltraReach Internet Corporation has the discretion to occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the “updated” date at the top of this Privacy page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect our users’ safety and privacy. Your continued use of the services constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.<br>    <br>4. CONTACTING US<br>    <br>    If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please contact us: info89 @ ultrasurf.us<br>    <br><br>UltraReach Internet Corporation will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly respond and resolve any problem or question. |

Copyright © 2024 UltraReach Internet Corp. U.S.A. All Rights Reserved.
